<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Pages on TransportChain</title><link>https://transportchain.io/page/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on TransportChain</description><image><title>TransportChain</title><url>https://transportchain.io/papermod-cover.png</url><link>https://transportchain.io/papermod-cover.png</link></image><generator>Hugo -- 0.146.7</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:49:23 +0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://transportchain.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Technology</title><link>https://transportchain.io/page/technology/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:49:23 +0400</pubDate><guid>https://transportchain.io/page/technology/</guid><description>&lt;p>The transportation industry, especially aviation, is one of the most regulated industries in the world. Each country/jurisdiction have their own laws and regulations governing the cooperation of pilots, airlines, mechanics, aircraft manufacturers, etc.. This makes building a conventional solution for everyone close to impossible. Each jurisdiction or civil aviation authority will want full transparency and absolute control which is very hard to provide by an enterprise software solution built and maintained by a conventional company or even a consortium/non-profit.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://transportchain.io/page/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 16:37:42 +0400</pubDate><guid>https://transportchain.io/page/contact/</guid><description>&lt;p>We are open to partnerships with flight schools, airlines and aviation mechanics. If you are representing a business in the aviation industry contact us to discover our offering to your specific business case.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For collaboration or other inquiries please contact us at &lt;strong>&lt;a href="mailto:info@transportchain.io">info@transportchain.io&lt;/a>&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="development-contribution">Development Contribution&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The project is currently in closed source mode and will continue like this until the release of the first working component for testing purposes. However, regardless of the closed source aspect of the current codebase we are ready to discuss possible contributions be that organizational, business domain expertise or work on the codebase itself. If you are interested in the project and want to be a part of it let us know at &lt;strong>&lt;a href="mailto:collaboration@transportchain.io">collaboration@transportchain.io&lt;/a>&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>